{
  "easyquestions":  [
    {
      "question": "What is 4 × 3?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "12",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5 × 2?",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 × 1?",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 7 × 2?",
      "answer1": "14",
      "answer2": "12",
      "correct": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 × 4?",
      "answer1": "12",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 × 1?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2 × 5?",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9 × 1?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "10",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4 × 2?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "6",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3 × 3?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "9"
    }
  ]
}
